♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
Okay.
Heads, it’s Odd first.
And tails, it’s Yumi.
Heads. Odd.
Huh, Yumi. I lose.
Hey Yumi, are you okay?
What am I doing over here, huh?
Uh, I, uh… I think we got a little problem here.
Well?
I guess there’s a little bug in the rematerialization program.
You call this a little bug? We can’t stay this way!
Well, what if we went back to Lyoko and devirtualized all over again?
Maybe everything will go back to normal.
And what if the program messes up again, and you don’t have any bodies
at all this time?
Uh, okay. Bad idea.
Uh, so what do we do then?
Gotta fix the program.
How long will it take you? A couple of hours at the most?
Um, if I work through the night, it might be ready by tomorrow morning.
What? You mean that I’m gonna have to sleep in a guy’s body?
Well, I’m not gonna get any sleep at all, I’ll have you know!
And if you haven’t noticed, I have a dynamite body! Better than yours!
For example, something’s itching in my back. It’s a…
I think it’s the strap to your--
Don’t you dare take it off, you hear?
Don’t you guys worry about it, I’ll be helping Jeremie tonight.
Everything will be fine by tomorrow morning.
I hope so.
Not as much as I do.
Okay, so what’s my schedule for this evening?
Well, try the three B’s - bacon, bath, bedtime.
What about me?
Same here, but Japanese style. Just try not to say anything stupid in front of
my parents. Can you even use chopsticks?
Yeah, as long as they look like forks.
Ha ha, very funny. Don’t do anything stupid with my body either!
Mine’s still under warranty!
I think you better brush your teeth and go to bed early tonight.
Isn’t tonight the night you’re supposed to break up with Magali?
Yeah, that’s right. And with Claire, too.
You’re going steady with two girls at the same time? I didn’t know that.
Neither do Magali and Claire. Not until now, that is.
Hey! I’ve got a great idea!
You’re always too shy to ask Yumi out, right?
Now you can practice on me!
Odd, that’s not a great idea, it's a stupid idea.
And anyway, I’m not that crazy about Yumi.
Yeah, right, tell me about it.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity for you to give it a shot without really sticking your neck out!
And this way, I can give you some pointers, too.
Pointers, you?
Come on, ask me out. I’m waiting.
Well, look who’s here. Romeo and Juliet.
Sissi, I can’t believe it. What a lamebrain.
My dear Ulrich, when will you understand that I am the girl for you?
What do you see in this string bean, anyway?
At least I don’t have the mind of a vegetable!
Huh?
Give it a rest, Sissi. Ulrich and I were made for one another. You got that?
Why, that- that- that… that’s disgusting!
Oh wow, the scoop of the year! I’ve got it!
What?
Hey, now I see why Sissi’s so crazy about you.
Do that one more time, and you’re dead.
Well.
You try to do a friend a favor, and that’s the thanks you get.
(GROWLS)
No, that’s not it.
Cut it out, Kiwi. There’s no reason to growl, it’s me, Yumi.
Ah, this should be it! Time to go. See you later, Kiwi.
(BARKS)
Be a good, now. Goodbye, Kiwi.
Odd!
What?
Ow!
I know all about Claire. You’re so… despicable!
Ugh…
Odd! I know all about Magali! You sneaky rat!
Odd?
Huh?
You can tell Ulrich he’ll have to beg for a date with a real flower once his
string bean veggie drops him!
Mhmm.
Hey, Yumi!
What are you doing? Did you find it?
Uh, yeah, here it is.
Sissi just told me to tell you something,
something about veggies?
I didn’t get it. What’s going on?
Nothing. Are you coming? Let’s go to the cafeteria.
Ulrich, do you mind answering a few questions for our academy gossip column?
Yes, I do mind.
What has gotten into you now?
Ask that imbecile, Odd.
Well, did you find it? I’ve had it ever since I was really little.
Why, Yumi, what’s the matter?
Huh?
Only in case of emergency, okay?
Hm.
(LAUGHS)
Um… actually, I’m- I’m- I’m not very hungry,
so, uh, I better go to bed.
再見
Why is she speaking to us in Chinese now?
It’s love, hahaha! Oh Ulrich, I wuv you!
Hiroki!
Huh?
You’ll see. You’ll get used to me in no time. Nice puppy.
Yumi, are you okay?
I-I thought my hand was disappearing for a minute. I must’ve imagined it.
Oh.
Don’t worry, you can tell Jeremie about it tomorrow morning.
Yeah, I guess it can wait.
Watch yourself.
Watch what?
Oh- awwww! Aw, gross!
I warned you. It’s more powerful than a laser arrow.
I was right, Aelita. It’s definitely a bug in the rematerialization program.
Huh? Aelita?
Oh, please, Kiwi!
Uh, Ulrich…
I hope that Jeremie found the bug.
Yumi, are you up? Could you give me a hand with breakfast?
Uh, yes, if…
If I had a hand to give you.
It only lasted a few seconds, but my hands completely disappeared.
Strange. I’ll be a lot happier when both of you are back in your own bodies.
I fixed the program. We just need to restart it from Lyoko.
We’ll go to the factory at lunchtime.
See? Everything’s fine.
Uh, no. Everything’s very bad.
Ni-hao!
Huh?
First of all, that’s Chinese, and second of all, what is with that outfit?
Well, they’re your clothes. Cool, huh? Looks really good.
You are so lucky that you’re in my body right now,
or I would beat you to a pulp!
Go home, you hear,
and change before the entire school sees you!
Yumi Ishiyama, transformed by love! Cool headline, huh?
It’ll double our circulation!
What are they talking about with this love thing?
Um… no time to explain! Don’t wanna be late for math class!
Sayonara!
Take out your pens, please. Pop quiz on linear functions.
Oh man, bad break. Yumi’s gonna kill me.
Do you always have conversations with yourself?
Well, yes, they call it a split personality, but nothing to worry about.
Right, is that why you’re dressed like that?
Well, um… kind of.
Uh, ma’am, I have a sore throat, can I go to the infirmary?
Uh, yes, of course, Yumi. Go ahead.
No one noticed anything in class?
No, they were all concentrating on the math quiz.
Huh? There was a math quiz this morning? Did you manage?
Well, if you mean sharpening my pencils and all that, yeah.
What do you think the problem is, Jeremie?
Odd and Yumi have been rematerialized in bodies that aren't their own,
and so they aren't stable.
And?
If we don’t take care of the problem immediately, their atoms might split.
What do you mean, our atoms might split?
Complete disintegration.
Great.
Head for the scanner room. I’m sending you down to the Ice Sector.
You’ll have to get to a waytower
due north from where you arrive.
Aelita will reboot the program from that tower,
and the nightmare should be over.
Aelita and Ulrich, you go in first.
Transfer, Ulrich!
Transfer, Aelita!
Virtualization!
Transfer, Odd-- no, I mean,
that is, uh, Yumi-- uh, no, wait, um…
Oh whatever.
Transfer, scanner, virtualization!
And now, let’s hear it for Catwoman…
(LAUGHTER)
There’s the tower!
Hurry up! XANA might want to send a welcome committee.
Be right back!
I hope Aelita makes it fast! This is turning into an emergency here!
Kankrelats. That’s all we need.
Gee, thanks for the heads up, Jeremie.
Sorry, but... watch it. Whatever happens, Odd or Yumi can’t be devirtualized.
If they go, it’s bye-bye for good.
Laser arrow!
But… hey… oh no, I forgot!
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
Super sprint!
Odd, how do the arrows work?
Well, you imagine you’re firing. You concentrate a little bit, and bingo! It fires!
Like this?
Hey!
Oops, sorry.
Uh, Jeremie, we’ve got a big problem! I can’t do anything from here!
The program’s being run by inhibitors!
We have to deactivate them! I’ll try to find them!
Oh no!
Thank you for caring.
We’re doing all we can, you know.
Hurry, we have to get to Sector Five!
Huh? But what for?
I’ll explain on the way. I’m bringing up your vehicles.
Are you absolutely sure we have to go into Sector Five?
We don’t have time for me to try and crack the millions of codes to
find those inhibitors.
Remember, if you don’t get back into your old bodies quickly,
it means disintegration!
And what’s more, seeing how you handled those arrows, you might
accidentally kill Odd before then!
Are you ready? I’m entering the code Scipio.
A Megatank!
Ulrich!
Oh, I can’t believe I could possibly be so dumb.
Holosphere system connected.
Ugh, I feel like I’m gonna be sick.
Oh yeah, the transporter does make me feel like throwing up.
Tough break for you.
Watch out, the wall is about to open!
Well?
The countdown has started, so hurry it up!
And watch out for the Scyphozoa!
Problem here!
XANA’s a pretty lame architect, he forgot to put the stairs in!
There’s the key!
Great, anyone know how to fly?
Great shot, you missed a Creeper ten yards in a hallway?
Wow, cool!
XANA’s modified the gravity in this room!
Hey!
Odd, move it! We’re coming to the end of the countdown!
Darn, I didn’t get enough momentum!
Odd, what are you doing?
Can’t you see? I’m swimming through guacamole!
Shield!
How many life points do you have left?
Lots, why?
Great job!
Bullseye!
Look out! Creepers behind you!
Aelita, no!
Aelita, the Scyphozoa!
Oh no, not now!
Aelita!
Yes!
Phew.
You okay, Aelita?
Yeah.
Here I go.
Jeremie, every time we dematerialize, it lasts longer and longer.
Aelita better find the code, and fast!
Careful, a Creeper!
Aelita, what’s going on?
I’m almost there!
Quick, deactivate the inhibitors as fast as you can and
don’t hang around there too long! Things are gonna get messy!
Ow!
No…
Aelita, hurry!
They’re in the final stage of disintegration.
Ugh!
Hurry up, Aelita!
That’s it! Done, Jeremie! You can take over again now!
Okay, I’ve got it! I’ll transfer back to the rematerialization program.
Yumi, no!
I sure hope the tweak on the rematerialization program worked.
I’m going to to the scanner room.
Odd! Is that… is that you?
Of course. What’s the matter with you? Don’t you recognize your own friends?
Dork.
It’s okay, Jeremie, we’ve got full recovery!
Great!
Heads, it’s Yumi who shows up first. Tails, and it’s Odd.
Tails!
Tails it is.
Yumi wasn’t too mad at me in the end. I mean, about her parents,
or the math quiz, or the clothes, or for taking a couple of slaps.
She is really cool.
You oughta go out with her.
Speak of, uh… did you tell her what happened between us?
No way! I plan on staying alive, good buddy.
Why? What did happen between you?
Oh, nothing.
Hey, speaking of Yumi, look. She’s over there with the school paper.
Uh-oh.
I don’t like this.
Odd.
Ulrich, help me!
I warned you. Sorry I can’t give you any pointers, good buddy.
ODD!
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS